hageltech.com 2017-06-25

# Hagel Technlologies web site privacy policy

Hagel Technologies has created this Privacy Policy Statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our web site (www.hageltech.com). 

## What we gather from visitors to our site

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. The company that hosts our web site logs and reports to us the IP addresses of visitors to our site. We use this information to generate general statistics about the hits on our site. 

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, Hagel Technologies employs software programs to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a file that a web site transfers to a visitor's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on certain pages to tailor our content better for returning visitors. You can disable cookies in your browser if you want, and most of our web site will still function properly. 

## Google Analytics

We are committed to ensuring that our website contains content that is valuable and useful to our customers and potential customers who visit. To assist us in this, we have implemented the Google analytics demographics and interest reporting features on our website. These tools allow us to review anonymous data regarding the gender, age and interests of website visitors and adapt our website content to better reflect their needs. This information is not provided to us in a personally-identifiable format. This means we cannot identify what information is abouat you personally, and we will not try to figure that out. 

You can always opt-out of Google Analytics data collection by using the [Google Ad Settings](https://www.google.ca/settings/ads) or through [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

## How Your personal information is treated

Your name and e-mail are used if you elect to receive updates and special offers via e-mail from Hagel Technologies. You can always "opt-out" from our mailing lists by contacting our staff or following the link in the email you received from us. 

## Links to other sites

Our policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control. For example, there are links on our web site to other web sites which we do not operate or control. These other sites may send cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. 

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Hagel Technologies Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the Hagel Technologies web site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

Our policy is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. If you have questions or concerns regarding this web site's privacy statement, please contact us. 

### Our policy at a glance

Hagel Technologies will never sell, rent, or share your personal information without your consent unless compelled by law or court order to do so.
